

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

I have experience in many things, however my current focuses are below:

Frontend

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT.JS, REDUX

Backend

EXPRESSJS, NOSQL(MONGODB), REST PATTERNS, AUTH, FIREBASE

MORE EXPERIENCE

GIT, PYTHON, FLASK, JQUERY, SQL, MYSQL, ANGULARJS, IONIC FRAMEWORK, REACT NATIVE, SOCKET.IO, SCSS,

FIND ME ON THE WEB



github.com/dirkdunn



linkedin.com/in/dirkdunn



dirkdunn.com

I am a motivated and experienced Developer, that puts expertise, insight, and ingenuity into building notable end to end web applications.

I look forward to the challenges I can solve for your organization.

For a more detailed view of my experience, please refer to my LinkedIn.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INSTRUCTOR

General Assembly | October 2016 - May 2017

FREELANCE DEVELOPMENT

Upwork | May 2016 - October 2016

WEB ENGINEER

Pitney Bowes | January 2015 - May 2016

CONTRACT DEVELOPER

Modis I June 2014 - December 2014

SECURITY ENGINEERING INTERNSHIP

SUNY | January 2014 - May 2014

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE
DUAL MAJORS IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AND PSYCHOLOGY
SUNY Plattsburgh